{
    "questions": [
	{
                "id": "1",
                "question": "A square rug has an area of 9 square feet. What is the perimeter of the rug? Perimeter = 2 x width + 2 x length",
                "option1": "3 feet",
                "option2": "6 feet",
                "option3": "9 feet",
                "option4": "12 feet",  

                "Correctans":"12"
        },    	
        {
                "id": "2",
                "question": "Which shows all the factors of 32?",
                "option1": " 1, 2, 4, 8, 16, 32",
                "option2": " 1, 2, 3, 16, 32",
                "option3": "1, 2, 16, 32",
                "option4": "1, 2, 4, 8, 12, 32",  

                "Correctans":" 1, 2, 4, 8, 16, 32"
        }, 
        {
                "id": "3",
                "question": "This angle measures 180 degrees.",
                "option1": "straight",
                "option2": "acute",
                "option3": "obtuse",
                "option4": " right",  

                "Correctans":"straight"
        }, 
        {
                "id": "4",
                "question": "To cut one shelf 24 centimetres long and two shelves 65 centimetres long from a single board, how long must the board be?",
                "option1": "103 cm long",
                "option2": "130 cm long",
                "option3": "154 cm long",
                "option4": "89 cm long",  

                "Correctans":"154 cm long"
        },  
        {
                "id": "5",
                "question": "A family can save $75 each month to buy a new TV which costs $675. How many months will it take before they can buy the TV?",
                "option1": "8 months",
                "option2": "11 months",
                "option3": "5 months",
                "option4": "9 months",  

                "Correctans":"9 months"
        }, 
        {
                "id": "6",
                "question": "15 samosas are needed for a party.; Each samosa will contain 2 ½ ounces of ground chicken. How much ground chicken will be needed?",
                "option1": "17 ½ ounces",
                "option2": "31 ½ ounces",
                "option3": "37 ½ ounces",
                "option4": "41 ½ ounces",  

                "Correctans":"37 ½ ounces"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "7",
                "question": "The ages of students in a math class are: 21, 23, 19, and 21. What is the average age of these students?",
                "option1": "Average age is 19",
                "option2": "Average age is 21",
                "option3": "Average age is 23",
                "option4": "Average age is 25",  

                "Correctans":"Average age is 21"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "8",
                "question": "34.6 x 100 =",
                "option1": "346.0",
                "option2": "34600.0",
                "option3": " 3460.0",
                "option4": "346000.0",  

                "Correctans":" 3460.0"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "9",
                "question": "2/3(7-4) + 8/9(10-1)",
                "option1": "5",
                "option2": "7",
                "option3": "10",
                "option4": "9",  

                "Correctans":"10"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "10",
                "question": "34+15-(-2-8)+4/2",
                "option1": "61",
                "option2": "50",
                "option3": "51",
                "option4": "41",  

                "Correctans":"61"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "11",
                "question": "3/2 + 4/8 - 3/4",
                "option1": "3/5",
                "option2": "4/5",
                "option3": "3/2",
                "option4": "5/4",  

                "Correctans":"5/4"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "12",
                "question": "2(8-5)+[1/2+(-12+10)]",
                "option1": "4",
                "option2": "2/3",
                "option3": "5/4",
                "option4": "9/2",  

                "Correctans":"9/2"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "13",
                "question": "6 x + 15 = 33,Solve for x.",
                "option1": "8",
                "option2": "3",
                "option3": "-3",
                "option4": "-8",  

                "Correctans":"3"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "14",
                "question": "3 y – 15 = –21, Solve for y.",
                "option1": "-12",
                "option2": "2",
                "option3": "-2",
                "option4": "12",  

                "Correctans":"-2"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "15",
                "question": "For which equation is the solution x = –3?",
                "option1": "–2 x + 7 = 13",
                "option2": "3 x – 2 = –7",
                "option3": "5 – 4 x = –7",
                "option4": "None of above.",  

                "Correctans":"–2 x + 7 = 13"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "16",
                "question": "Which of the following equations has a negative value for its variable?",
                "option1": "–3 x + 5 = 4",
                "option2": " 4 a – 12 = –8",
                "option3": " 5 y – 6 = –7",
                "option4": "None of avove.",  

                "Correctans":" 5 y – 6 = –7"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "17",
                "question": "3 y + 9 y – 24 = 6 y – 4 – 8 ",
                "option1": "2",
                "option2": "6",
                "option3": "-2",
                "option4": "-6",  

                "Correctans":"2"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "18",
                "question": "What is the largest number you can make using these digits: 5,1,9,2 ?",
                "option1": "5192",
                "option2": "1259",
                "option3": "9521",
                "option4": "9152",  

                "Correctans":"9521"
        },    	   	   
        {
                "id": "19",
                "question": "What number is half way between 29 & 37 ?",
                "option1": "33",
                "option2": "34",
                "option3": "35",
                "option4": "36",  

                "Correctans":"33"
        },  
        {
                "id": "20",
                "question": "Put these in order, starting with the smallest: 2.12, 2.3, 2.2 ,3.21",
                "option1": "3.21, 2.3, 2.22, 2.12",
                "option2": "2.3, 2.12, 2.22, 3.21",
                "option3": "2.22, 2.3, 3.21, 2.12",
                "option4": "2.12, 2.22, 2.3, 3.21",  
 
                "Correctans":"2.12, 2.22, 2.3, 3.21"
        },    	   	      
        {
                "id": "21",
                "question": "Which of these is a solution of 3x + 8 = 23",
                "option1": "x=2",
                "option2": "x=3",
                "option3": "x=4",
                "option4": "x=5",  

                "Correctans":"x=5"
        }]
}		

